Hello everyone! Welcome to a special jumpsuit up because it is another latex
jumpsuit you can see here and there are a few specialties I want to mention in
the beginning. So first I have to say thank you to everyone who supported me
on Ko-fi because this catsuit was a Ko-fi goal and I was able to order it thanks
to you and second I ordered it from latex crazy but I said please do not make the ruffles at the
neck or the arms because the design was slightly different so I altered it a bit and also the
colors are really cool and I chose them myself but yeah I think I'll change into it I already
washed it today so there's no talcum here anymore and I used latex shiner
already so it's already shiny and I can be faster when I get into it. Here I am
wearing this catsuit. I'm so happy because it fits so good. I'm so relieved because it is my first real
real made to measure latex catsuit. Yeah after like seven years of wearing latex this is the
first real made to measure from head to toe customized latex catsuit and I love it. It fits
so good and it looks so good. I'm totally totally in love with the design. I'm so glad that I said
please no ruffles here or here and that I chose these colors this is metallic
black then we have translucent lilac here and electric rose for the trims so
mix of different latex manufacturers as well but I think they work great
together and I love the slightly translucent part here normally I'm not a fan of
translucent latex. Still definitely not a fan of natural translucent latex but
like color translucent like this here or black translucent is okay and I think it
really makes a nice cleavage and in general this suit makes nice boobs.
Also from the back side I think these trims down the whole body they emphasize
figure even more. Happy me! I know that I'm definitely going to wear this one for
fetish parties and stuff because it's super comfortable it's not too short
doesn't sit too tight anywhere it's just like kind of perfect and again I'm glad
it turned out this way because I ordered it in January in the beginning of
January and the manufacturer already said we have lots to do so you have to
wait a couple of weeks so I'm glad I waited that long because it turned out
so good although I have to say if you're a latex manufacturer and you're in close
contact with your clients do tell them if the order is going to be delayed
because I waited for like an additional eight weeks and it would have been nice
if there would have been an email like hey sorry it's taking a bit longer and then I would have
been like okay at least I know that it's taking longer but yeah apparently I heard that a lot of
latex labels have a lot to do and customers have to wait everywhere apparently people like latex
touching up the shine a bit with this cool swipe thingy which is totally infused with
shining product I noticed in the last video I did for the all about latex
topic that I constantly was like yeah tell me more oil oil oil oil and everyone
in the comments was like what oil is it can I use normal oil and no definitely
don't use normal kitchen oil or stuff like that because latex needs special
oil, latex shiner, silicon oil or especially developed products like these from Becloth
which I use and no normal kitchen oils and stuff like that because they will destroy
your latex so be careful.
It is a material you need to take care of but then it'll last and look good.
so again thanks to all of you who supported me on ko-fi i'm going to take your exclusive pictures
now in a sec and i'll send it to you if you want to support me and my channel check out the links
down below in this video for example for my patreon or another coffee goal maybe in the future
And then we can all look forward to new videos with new cool stuff.
I hope you liked this one.
Leave a comment down below if you like this catsuit or how do you like the color combination.
Do you love it as much as I do?
Tell me down below and have a nice day.
See you around.
Bye!